What do we want to do with it?
我们要用它来做些什么？
Well, we've been playing around with GitHub so much,
我们一直在大量使用 GitHub
we've been looking at all these good hubs.
一直在看这些 GitHub
It's time for us to join GitHub with our own with our first repository.
现在是时候让我们亲自加入 GitHub 创造属于我们自己的第一个仓库了
Let's go ahead and let's make this happen
让我们来实现这个目标
in the lesson seven full blockchain solidity course, yes,
在 "full-blockchain-solidity-course-js" 的 "Lesson 7" 中
there is a link to this GitHub Quickstart
有一个到 "Github Quickstart" 的链接
that we're going to follow to set up our first repository.
我们可以参照它来设置我们的首个仓库
This is going to be the moment where you are starting to build your portfolio
现在是时候开始创建你的档案了
building and GitHub is borderline crucial for your development journey.
建立一个 GitHub 对你的开发之旅来说至关重要
It's going to be your portal folio, it's going to be where you say,
它会成为你的档案，你可以在这里告诉其他人
Hey, look at all the cool products that I'm engaging with, that I'm working with, that I'm participating in.
嘿，看看我参与和从事的炫酷产品
If you've already made GitHub before,
如果你之前就用过 GitHub
I highly recommend you still push this up to GitHub
我强烈建议你仍然要把这些成果推送到 GitHub 上
as proof that you've done it.
它可以证明你做到了
And then you can also tweet it at me saying, hey, look how far I've gotten.
你还可以到 Twitter 上说一下，嘿，看看我走了多远！
Look where I've done, look at how fantastic I'm learning smart contracts,
看看我智能合约学的多好！
and be incredibly excited about now,
然后好好兴奋一下吧
this quickstart will walk you through creating a repository, creating a branch and teaching all this stuff,
这个 Quickstart 会引导你创建仓库，创建分支，并教给你所有这些东西
we're going to follow the instructions from the GitHub documentation
我们将按照 GitHub 的这个文档说明进行操作
about adding locally hosted code to GitHub,
即“添加本地托管代码到 GitHub”
("Adding locally hosted code to GitHub")
we already have a project, and we're just pushing it up.
我们已经有了一个项目，现在只用把它推送上来就行了
Since the Windows users are using WsL,
由于 Windows 用户用的是 WSL
you can just follow the Mac or Linux instructions here,
所以你可以直接参照 Mac 和 Linux 的说明进行操作
the first thing that we're going to do is in your GitHub profile,
我们要做的第一件事是来到你的 GitHub 的 "profile" 页面
or your GitHub login,
或是你的 GitHub 登录页面
we're gonna hit this little plus thing, and hit new repository,
我们要点击这里的小加号并点击 "New repository"
you can call this whatever you want, let's call it hard hat, fund me b code camp,
你可以随意命名，我命名为 "hardhat-fund-me-fcc"
you can put a description if you want,
如有需要你还可以添加描述("Description")
learning from recode camp, and Patrick, about smart contracts.
跟着 FCC & Patrick 一起学习智能合约！！！
("Learning from FCC & Patrick about Smart Contracts!!!")
We'll make it public because we want other people to see you being fantastic and learning smart contracts.
我们设置为公开("Public")，因为我们希望其他人能看到你学习智能合约的杰出表现
We'll leave this blank, and we'll hit Create repository.
这个部分我们留白，接着点击 "Create repository"
Now, this is our public code repository.
现在，这就是我们的公开代码仓库了
This is our first one,
这是我们的首个仓库
if you've done these already, this will be your first smart contract one.
如果你以前有过的话，那这个就是你的首个智能合约仓库
It even has some instructions in here, too, that teaches us how to create a new repository from the command line,
这里甚至还有一些说明，它在教我们如何在命令行中创建一个新的仓库
you can follow this if you want, or you can follow like so
你可以跟着这个来做，也可以跟着我来做
the first thing we're going to do is we're going to initialize a git branch.
我们要做的第一件事是初始化一个 git 分支
And from way back when you should already have Git installed.
很久之前，你应该就已经安装好 git 了
Remember, you can check by running git dash dash version like this.
你可以像这样，运行 `git --version` 来进行检查
Git is a little different from GitHub,
git 和 GitHub 还是有一点不同的
Git is known as version control.
git 就是所谓的版本控制系统("Version Control")
And it allows us to make changes to our code, but keep a history of all the code changes that we've made.
它可以让我们在更改代码后保留全部的代码更改历史
GitHub is a place where we can push all of these changes and keep track of all of our code.
而 GitHub 则是我们推送更改和跟踪代码的地方
So the first thing that we're going to do is we're going to create a new branch.
所以我们的第一件事就是创建一个新的分支
And I'm not going to explain Git and working with Git too, too deeply.
我不打算过于深入地介绍和使用 git
But if you want to learn about Git
但如果你想学习有关 git 的知识的话
Free Code Camp, of course, has a video on Git and GitHub for beginners.
"freeCodeCamp" 有一个关于 git 和 GitHub 的面向初学者的视频
So we're going to create this new branch with git init dash b main,
我们来创建一下这个新分支 `git init -b main`
now your Visual Studio code might automatically start formatting some stuff.
你的 Visual Studio Code 可能会自动开始做一些格式化
And if it does, that's great. And if it doesn't,
don't worry about it. But what you'll see here on the left is
you'll see some stuff is green, and some stuff is gray, open
back up that dot Git ignore, you'll see that all the gray
stuff is the stuff that we have in this dot Git ignore this is
intentional, this is what we want. This is just some some
highlighting saying, hey, this green stuff is what you're
working with on GitHub. And this gray stuff is what you're not
working with and GitHub. And that's what we want. You don't
need to push artifacts, or cash or coverage or node modules,
people can install and compile on their own machines, we
definitely don't want to push up our Dotty and V if we're using a
Dotty and V. And we don't really need to push up coverage dot
JSON, either the rest of this we do. So now what's next, after we
initialize our main branch, you now should be able to run git
status in your terminal and see this huge red output of all
these things that are untracked, and we don't have any commits
for, what we can do now is we can stage all of our code with
git add period, and then commit it with Git commit, we're going
to run these one at a time instead of together. Before I
run git add, I'm going to add deployments to this list too,
because GitHub doesn't really need to know about all the
different deployments I make, especially when I make a ton of
deployments to my local hosts, they don't need to know. So
we're going to add that to, then we're going to run git add dot.
And if we do a git status, now, we can see all of our code has
been staged for being committed for being a part of this history
of our code. And then take a quick look at all these files
and make sure your dot E and V file is not and never in here.
So now we're going to run git commit dash m and then this
message for our commit, okay, so we'll run git commit dash m, we
can say, initial commit, or whatever you want in this
message here, first commit, initial commit, who cares, and
it's gonna say, create mode, blah, blah, blah, for all of
these files. And if we do git status, now, it's blank on
branch main, nothing to commit. And then you might get something
like this. If you've never worked with Git before your name
and email were added automatically. We're a little
bit confused here. We'll talk about this in just a second. So
next, what we can do is we're actually going to copy the URL
of our GitHub repo. So you can grab that just by copying here
or right at the top, that URL right there. And what we're
going to do is we're going to add this as a remote repo. To do
that. We'll do git remote add, and we'll give this remote repo
a name. For us. We'll say origin and then we'll paste that URL
there. We're now saying the the origin remote repo is good.
Gonna be at this URL, we run git remote dash v, we can see that
the origin repo for fetching is at this branch. And the origin
repo for pushing is also at this branch. So when we want to get
new code, a fetch code will fetch it from here. And if we
want to push code up, we want to give code to the GitHub. We'll
also get it from here. So now we've set the new remote with
that remote URL. Now we're going to actually push the changes to
github.com. And the way we do that is with Git push, and we
pick which remote we want to push to, and we're going to push
the origin. And then which branch we want to push to which
we're going to push to Maine, it'll probably prompt you for
your username and your password, and maybe your email and
everything. Now, if authentication doesn't work for
you, for some reason, you can come over to Settings. Or if you
scroll down to developer settings, Personal Access Tokens
and create generate new token, some token,
give yourself repo access, write access, and hit Generate token.
And try to use this token as your password. Instead, be sure
to use the GitHub documentation and the GitHub discussion
associated with this course, if you get lost or if something
doesn't work, as shown here. But once it's done, once you add all
that information in correctly, you come back to your get up and
you will have your first GitHub repo with all the code and
everything in it like this. And once you complete this step,
once you do this, you should absolutely celebrate. If you
like, you can shoot a tweet web three community in the
blockchain community is absolutely this collaborative
space. So Twitter crypto is where a lot of these people
congregate to share ideas. So definitely be sure to celebrate
and share this and be really, really excited. And shoot a
tweet out like this. Give your friends a high five, share it on
Twitter, share it on Discord shared on Reddit, be excited for
how far you've gotten, we've got a lot more to go. But by
completing this part, you have done fantastically, and I'm so
excited for you to start the next section. Now, we're not
going to go over the TypeScript addition to this because there's
nothing really new here. However, again, if you want to
see TypeScript, feel free to jump into the GitHub repository
associated with this course.